你好。
Hello.
我，名叫 Phileo
I, am Phileo
我要给你演奏一首歌
I'm going to play a song for you
有关那位敏捷，彩虹色的马儿
about the fast, rainbow-y horse
但首先，我得邀请你加入我，
But first, I must ask you to join me,
一起到世上最艳丽的小马聚会
at the world's most alluring pony convention
「Equestria 洛杉矶」
"Equestria LA"
就在今年(2013)的五月
happening this May
也或许，你可能会更想给自己看看
Or perhaps, you'd prefer to feast your eyes
我的搞笑时刻，跟「马迷俱乐部」一起
upon my silly times with the Brony Clubhouse
这是什么！？
What is this!?
嘘...安静点，甜心(西班牙文)
Shhhh, silencio mi amor
这首歌并非由吉他开始，
For this song does not begin with a guitar,
而是在那小小的黑胶机上
but on the humble vinyl record
就比如说这边这台
Much like this one here
来吧，朋友们，
Come with me my friends,
我们的冒险，启程。
our journey beings.
来，我们学了什么
Now, what have we learned
很多的控制
Lots of control
很好
Good
大声尖叫
Screaming and hollering
对，而最重要的是
Yes, and most importantly
热情
Passion
嘿
Right
那现在你知道欢呼的元素
So now that you know the elements of a good cheer
来，听一个
let's, hear one
一...二...三...
1... 2... 3...
上！
GO!
一道红色
Flash of red
鬼神的她飞上天
the spectral wonder takes flight
她很确定，她很坚定，她感觉很爽
and she's ready and she's steady and she's feelin' just right
她有热情，有动力，有决心要赢
She got the passion, the drive, the tenacity to win
而只要十秒她就能让你头昏眼花
and in 10 seconds flat she'll take your head for a spin
天如火烧，仿佛渐渐变成一颗密桃
Sky is burnin' and it's turnin' to a tangerine peach
好像在海南岛沙滩的太阳下山
like a sun slowly settin' over Huntington Beach
她的肚子里有颗火
She's got a fire in her belly
嘿！
Yep!
眼睛里有火
fire in her eyes
对！
Yes!
超音速的步伐在空中留下火迹
supersonic strut leaves a fire in the skies
越发亮，变成温暖的金光
Brighten up to a warm and golden glow
让他充满你的从脚到头
let it fill you all up from your head to your toe
让那太阳闪在你头
let that sun shine down on ya
大家都叫大声点
everypony scream louder
七彩在天空中
7 colors in the sky
看他飞过天空
Watch her dash on by
天堂被遮住
The heavens are covered
被如此的景色
with so many wonders
我爱她的飞相
I love the way she flies
吼，你要这样给我喊加油？
Urgh, you're gonna cheer for me like that?
大声点
Louder
耶
Yay
大声点
Louder
耶
Yay
大声点！！！
LOUDER!!!
有片青青草地
We got the green green grass
还有翡翠绿树
and the emerald trees
还有平原上的兔子、鸟儿，跟蜜蜂
and the meadows with the bunnies and the birds and the bees
而我，真希望能从她的角度看看
and I wish I could see it from her point of view
直接从那，一大片蓝天的中间
straight up there in the middle of the big ol' blue
要是可以我一定还会带你去
and I would if I could and I would take you too
飞过永恒森林，到坎特拉城去
over the Everfree Forest to a Canterlot view
飞到高空中，进入靛色的夜
Flying high up in the sky into the indigo night
星星映照在你的紫色目珠，没有碍眼物
with the stars in your violet eyes and no care in sight
我没有任何烦恼
I ain't got no care in sight
当我和你
when I'm with you
我没有任何烦恼
I ain't got no care in sight
当我和你
when I'm with you
我没有任何烦恼
I ain't got no care in sight
当我和你
when I'm with you
When I'm with you
七彩在天空中
7 colors in the sky
看他飞过天空
Watch her dash on by
天堂被遮住
The heavens are covered
被如此的景色
with so many wonders
我爱她的飞相
I love the way she flies
上吧！
C'mon!
天使飞
Angels fly
冲向边
Dashing by
闭上眼
Close your eyes
拥抱天
Feel the skies
七彩在天空中
7 colors in the sky
看他飞过天空
Watch her dash on by
天堂被遮住
The heavens are covered
被如此的景色
with so many wonders
我爱她的飞相
I love the way she flies
天使飞
Angels fly
冲向边
Dashing by
闭上眼
Close your eyes
拥抱天
Feel the skies
（别忘了要订阅！）
还有，看看底下关于 Equestria LA 的资讯
以及马迷俱乐部
... 对，这是 comic sans*!
* comic sans: 一个被厌恶的字体
相当于标楷体或细明体